http://www.diverseworks.org/support-diverseworks/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
DiverseWorks collects identifiable information to fulfill online orders and registrations. The types of personal information collected are: name, shipping and billing addresses, email address, phone number, and credit card information (when applicable).
DiverseWorks respects privacy and complies with international regulations. DiverseWorks does not share any financial or personal information you provide when registering for an event or making a donation, except as required by law or to acknowledge your donation on our website and our publications, if agreed.
DiverseWorks will never share or sell its mailing lists or email lists with any third parties or advertisers.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How You Can Access, Correct or Withdraw Your Information
You may request any personally identifiable information that we collect by contacting DiverseWorks at info@diverseworks.org, or by telephone at (713) 223-8346. You may correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error. You have the right to remove any and all of your information from DiverseWorks. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (713) 223-8346 or send us an email at info@diverseworks.org.
Upcoming
A HUMAN LOOK AT 288: WALKING TOUR
December 20, 2020 10:30 am
Register
View All Events
3400 Main Street, Suite 292  |  Houston, Texas 77002  |  713.223.8346
